edwardkhoo.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Your Privacy is a priority at EdwardKhoo.com. Your personal information will never be given or sell to anyone.

1\. The only information that will be collected on this blog is as follows:

Your IP (that is to say, your computer’s individual identification number) will be logged on server when you visit this blog.

If you choose to leave comments in the comments section then, at your option, ‘cookie’ is used to recognise you. A ‘cookie’ is a small amount of data which is send to your computer. The data is then stored on your browser or hard disk. The cookie is only activated at your request and if you wish to activate it, you may do so by indicating ‘Yes’ in the ‘Remember Me’ function which you will find in each Comments Window. Most web browsers can be set to prevent you from receiving new cookies, notify you before accepting cookies or disable cookies altogether. Details about this can normally be found in the Help facility provided with your browser.

If you choose to leave your email address in your comments it will be viewable to other readers – you do so at your own risk of others using it for their own purposes. Leaving your email address in comments is completely optional.

If you choose to subscribe to my Mailing List then your name and e-mail address will be stored in which information will only be used to provide you with our e-mail newsletter and similar updates and bulletins.

2\. You can ask me to update or remove your personal information by sending an email through our contact form.

3\. This privacy policy is applicable only to this blog and does not apply to any other blogs or websites to which I may be linked.

* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
